{
    "subject": "resource/Zakarid_Armenia",
    "predicate": "property/commonName",
    "object": "Zakarids",
    "human_readable": "The common name of Zakarid Armenia is Zakarids.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831995964050293,
            "question": "What is the common name for Zakarid Armenia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8426331877708435,
            "question": "What is another name for the Zakarids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7772390246391296,
            "question": "What is the significance of the name 'Zakarids'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5524081587791443,
            "question": "Are there any significant cultural traditions associated with the Zakarids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5319347381591797,
            "question": "What is known about the history of the Zakarids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317001938819885,
            "question": "Where are the Zakarids located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5066275596618652,
            "question": "How did the Zakarids influence Armenian culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4965595602989197,
            "question": "Is Zakarids a historical region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36928096413612366,
            "question": "Are there any modern-day communities associated with the Zakarids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36854520440101624,
            "question": "What are some key events in the history of the Zakarids?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The common name of Zakarid Armenia is Zakarids.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8741_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any modern-day communities associated with the Zakarids?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8741_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Zakarids a historical region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8741_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Zakarids influence Armenian culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8741_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8741_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can evaluate the triple \"The common name of Zakarid Armenia is Zakarids\".\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* Document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8741/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt mentions \"Zakarid Armenia (Armenian language: \u0536\u0561\u0584\u0561\u0580\u0575\u0561\u0576 \u0540\u0561\u0575\u0561\u057d\u057f\u0561\u0576 Zakaryan Hayastan)\" as the common name of the principality.\n* Document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8741/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt mentions \"Zakarid Armenia\" as the common name of the principality.\n\nHowever, none of these documents mention \"Zakarids\" as a common name for Zakarid Armenia. The documents do mention \"The Zakarids\" as a term referring to the ruling dynasty or nobility of Zakarid Armenia.\n\nTherefore, my evaluation is:\n\n`{ 'output': 'no' }`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The common name of Zakarid Armenia is Zakarids\" can be supported by the information in documents, as document `60.txt` and `52.txt` refer to the period as \"Zakarid Armenia\" or \"Zakaryan Hayastan,\" which implies that \"Zakarids\" or \"Zakaryans\" are indeed used as common names for this principality."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The text states \"Zakarid Armenia (Armenian language: \u0536\u0561\u0584\u0561\u0580\u0575\u0561\u0576 \u0540\u0561\u0575\u0561\u057d\u057f\u0561\u0576 Zakaryan Hayastan), was an Armenian principality between 1201 and 1360, ruled by the Zakarian dynasty\" which does not mention the name \"Zakarids\", but rather \"Zakarian\".",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}